addonsolutions.com 2016-11-08

# Privacy Policy - Addon Solutions

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience. 

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form or enter information on our site. 

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * __To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * __To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  * __To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.

**How We Protect Your Information?**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. Our Site is in compliance with PCI vulnerability standards in order to create as secure of an environment as possible for Users. 

**Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. 

**We use cookies to:**

Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third party services that track this information on our behalf. You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It won't affect the users experience that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders. 

**Third Party Disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. 

**Third party links**

We do not include or offer third party products or services on our website. 

**We have implemented the following:**

  * __Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * __Google Display Network Impression Reporting
  * __Demographics and Interests Reporting
  * __DoubleClick Platform Integration

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Optingout:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**How does our site handle do not track signals?**

We honor do not track signals and do not track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

**Does our site allow third party behavioral tracking?**

It's also important to note that we allow third party behavioral tracking.

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the India and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

**In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:**

We will notify the users via in site notification within 7 business days.

**SPAM Act**

The SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

**We collect your email address in order to:**

  * __Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * __Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original
  * __transaction has occurred

**To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM we agree to the following:**

  * __NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses
  * __Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way
  * __Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters
  * __Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * __Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly
  * __Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email

**If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at[info@addonsolutions.com](mailto:info@addonsolutions.com)**

Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

www.addonsolutions.com  
92/Sarovar Complex,  
B / H Samudra Annexi,   
Off C.G. Road, Navrangpura  
Ahmedabad, Gujarat, INDIA

##### **Our Certifications and Association**
